Giles R. Wright Papers
Giles R. Wright Papers
1929-1962
Wright, Giles R., fl. 1930-1962
1.0 linear feet
Papers of the American clergyman. Collection includes essays, notes, sermons, speeches, published material, and miscellany.
148766
Biographical History
Giles R. Wright was an American clergyman.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Giles R. Wright Papers is divided into three series. Miscellaneous includes, among other things, a folder of programs of church services in which Wright participated as minister. Published material contains magazine articles and newspaper clippings primarily of a religious nature. Writings contains notes and essays from Wright's college years as well as handwritten copies of his sermons and speeches as a minister.
Arrangement of the Collection
Material is arranged alphabetically by type within each series.
Subject and Genre Headings
Church and clergy; Wright, Giles R., fl. 1930-1962; Clergy, United States.; Programs (documents); Clippings (information artifacts); Sermons.; Theses.; Speeches (documents); Clergy.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Miscellaneous
  - Bulletin, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Church service programs, 1941-1961 (Box 1)
  - Poem (Box 1)
- Published material
  - Magazine articles, 1937-1945 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1940-1958 (Box 1)
- Writings
  - Educational notes, 1930-1953; 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Essays and theses, 1929-1947; 3 folders (Box 1, 2)
  - Exams, 1940-1942 (Box 2)
  - Fragments (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Sermons and speeches, 1936-1962; undated; 4 folders (Box 2)